Cultural Survival Records MS180
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Office files, 1919 -- 2013; MS180.004; 46.7 Linear Feet
  - A-Edd, 1953 -- 2010; MS180.004.001
    - Business Cards, 1995; MS180.004.007.00016 (Box 7)
    - Business for Social Responsibility & IPs, 2005; MS180.004.007.00017 (Box 7)
    - Butler, Joshua: China - 3 Gorges Dam, MS180.004.007.00018 (Box 7)
    - Butler, Joshua: "To be a Nation Under God: The United States and Indigenous Nations," Honors Thesis, Spring, 1999; MS180.004.007.00019 (Box 7)
    - CAEX, 1993 -- 1995; MS180.004.007.00020 (Box 7)
    - CAEX - Tropic, 1991 -- 1992; MS180.004.007.00021 (Box 7)
    - Calendar of Indian Social Events, 1998; MS180.004.007.00022 (Box 7)
    - Calendars, 2000 -- 2004; MS180.004.007.00023 (Box 7)
    - Camawari: La Plenada Research Station, 1992; MS180.004.007.00024 (Box 7)
      Includes sub-folders "Letters of Agreement, Appendices, Letters of Amendments"; Correspondence After Approval"; "Disbursement Requests"; and "Background Information Prior to Approval (proposal)".
    - Cameron Notes, 2010; MS180.004.007.00025 (Box 7)
    - Camp, Mark, 2003; MS180.004.007.00026 (Box 7)
    - Camp, Mark: Chicago AAA, 2003; MS180.004.007.00027 (Box 7)
    - Canada: Development Issues (See also James Bay Project) 1 of 2, 1977 -- 1994; MS180.004.007.00028 (Box 7)
    - Canada: Development Issues (See also James Bay Project) 2 of 2, 1982 -- 1990; MS180.004.007.00029 (Box 7)
    - Canada Indigenous Groups: Mohawk, 1990; MS180.004.007.00030 (Box 7)
    - Canada - James Bay (Activism) Burlington Declaration, 1991; MS180.004.008.00001 (Box 8)
    - Canada - James Bay (Activism) Cambridge Resolution, 1992; MS180.004.008.00002 (Box 8)
    - Canada - James Bay (Event) Ban the Dam Jam, 1991; MS180.004.008.00003 (Box 8)
    - Canada - James Bay (Info) N.E. Alliance - Energy Efficiency, 1992; MS180.004.008.00004 (Box 8)
    - Canada - James Bay (Legislative Activism) CS action - Mass S.336, 1992; MS180.004.008.00005 (Box 8)
    - Canada - James Bay (Orgs) Northeast Alliance to Protect James Bay, 1992; MS180.004.008.00006 (Box 8)
    - Canada - James Bay Useful Addresses, 1992; MS180.004.008.00007 (Box 8)
    - Canada: Kemano Affair, 1993 -- 1994; MS180.004.008.00008 (Box 8)
    - Canada: Lubicon Lake Background, 1982 -- 1984; MS180.004.008.00009 (Box 8)
    - Canada: Lubicon Lake Band Complaint to the UN, 1984 -- 1985; MS180.004.008.00010 (Box 8)
    - Canada: Lubicon Lake Boycott of the 1988 Calgary Winter Olympics, 1986; MS180.004.008.00011 (Box 8)
    - Canada: Lubicon Lake Boycott of the 1988 Calgary Winter Olympics Glenbow Exhibit, 1986; MS180.004.008.00012 (Box 8)
    - Canada: Lubicon Lake Court Documents, 1983 -- 1988; MS180.004.008.00013 (Box 8)
    - Canada: Lubicon Lake Federal Negotiations, 1983 -- 1986; MS180.004.008.00014 (Box 8)
    - Canada: Lubicon Lake General Historical Information, 1983 -- 1990; MS180.004.008.00015 (Box 8)
    - Canada: Lubicon Lake Ivany Investigation, 1984 -- 1986; MS180.004.008.00016 (Box 8)
    - Canada: Lubicon Lake Mimir Corp., 1984; MS180.004.008.00017 (Box 8)
    - Canadian Alliance in Solidarity with the Native Peoples, 1990 -- 1991; MS180.004.008.00018 (Box 8)
    - Candela, 1992 -- 1995; MS180.004.008.00019 (Box 8)
    - Caribbean: General, 1984 -- 1995; MS180.004.008.00020 (Box 8)
    - Castanha, 1991 -- 1993; MS180.004.008.00021 (Box 8)
    - Center for Amazon Community Ecology, 1995; MS180.004.008.00022 (Box 8)
    - Center for Andean Ethnomusicology - CAE - Correspondence, 2004; MS180.004.008.00023 (Box 8)
    - Center for Andean Ethnomusicology Project info, Contract, Finances, Annual Report, 2003 -- 2004; MS180.004.008.00024 (Box 8)
    - Central Am. Report - Honduras - CONPAH Info, 1997; MS180.004.008.00025 (Box 8)
    - Central Am. Report - Hopi/Navajo, 1997; MS180.004.008.00026 (Box 8)
    - Central Am. Report - Nigeria - Ogoni, 1994; MS180.004.008.00027 (Box 8)
    - Central Am. Report - North America, 1996 -- 1997; MS180.004.008.00028 (Box 8)
    - Central Amer. Report - Panama - Guaymí, 1996 -- 1997; MS180.004.008.00029 (Box 8)
    - Central America: Conflict I., 1984; MS180.004.008.00030 (Box 8)
    - Centre for Economic Botany Correspondence, 1996; MS180.004.008.00031 (Box 8)
    - Central America Contadora Pact, 1984 -- 1987; MS180.004.008.00032 (Box 8)
    - Central America Foreign Involvement, 1982; MS180.004.008.00033 (Box 8)
    - Central America General, 1981 -- 1996; MS180.004.008.00034 (Box 8)
    - Central America: Religion, 1983 -- 1989; MS180.004.008.00035 (Box 8)
    - Centro de Desarrollo y Avance, A.C., 1993; MS180.004.008.00036 (Box 8)
    - Chalker, 1990; MS180.004.008.00037 (Box 8)
    - Chapin, Mac - 501(c)(3) tax exempt letters from IRS, incoming and expense reports FY92, audit FY91, 1972 -- 1992; MS180.004.008.00038 (Box 8)
    - Chapin, Mac - AID/LAC-G-1350 Semi-Annual Reports, 1980 -- 1982; MS180.004.008.00039 (Box 8)
    - Chapin, Mac - Central America Program Grant management System (GMS), 1991; MS180.004.008.00040 (Box 8)
    - Chapin, Mac - Central America Program Grants and Priority Areas, 1991 -- 1992; MS180.004.008.00041 (Box 8)
    - Chapin, Mac - Central America Program Insurance, 1991 -- 1993; MS180.004.008.00042 (Box 8)
    - Chapin, Mac - Central America Program Staff Timesheets, 1991 -- 1993; MS180.004.008.00043 (Box 8)
    - Chapin, Mac - Central America Program Team Meeting Minutes, 1992; MS180.004.008.00044 (Box 8)
    - Chapin, Mac - Communications Software, 1990 -- 1992; MS180.004.008.00045 (Box 8)
    - Chapin, Mac - Contact List, 1992; MS180.004.008.00046 (Box 8)
    - Chapin, Mac - CS Proposals AID, 1979 -- 1986; MS180.004.008.00047 (Box 8)
    - Chapin, Mac - CVs - Field Rep, 1993; MS180.004.008.00048 (Box 8)
    - Chapin, Mac - Filing, 1992; MS180.004.008.00049 (Box 8)
    - Chapin, Mac - Fundraising, 1992; MS180.004.008.00050 (Box 8)
    - Chapin, Mac - Library Catalogue, 1992; MS180.004.008.00051 (Box 8)
    - Chapin, Mac - Mac's Travel Itineraries, 1992 -- 1993; MS180.004.008.00052 (Box 8)
    - Chapin, Mac - MOPAWI Congress (travel plans,), 1992; MS180.004.008.00053 (Box 8)
    - Chapin, Mac - Resumes, 1991 -- 1993; MS180.004.009.00001 (Box 9)
    - Chapin, Mac - Resumes - Administrative Assistant Applicants, 1992; MS180.004.009.00002 (Box 9)
    - Chapin, Mac - Resumes - Administrator Candidates, 1993; MS180.004.009.00003 (Box 9)
    - Chapin, Mac - Resumes - Costa Rica Office Admin. Asst. Candidates, 1992; MS180.004.009.00004 (Box 9)
    - Chiapas, 1996 -- 2000; MS180.004.009.00005 (Box 9)
    - Chiapas - Misc. Articles/Research, 1998 -- 1999; MS180.004.009.00006 (Box 9)
    - Chile: General, 1991 -- 1992; MS180.004.009.00007 (Box 9)
    - Chinchero Exhibition, 1982 -- 1997; MS180.004.009.00008 (Box 9)
    - Chincheros Project 81-PERU-35, 1981; MS180.004.009.00009 (Box 9)
    - Chippewa, 1987 -- 1991; MS180.004.009.00010 (Box 9)
    - Chole, E. and T. Mulat: Land Settlement in Ethiopia: A Review of Developments, 1984; MS180.004.009.00011 (Box 9)
    - Christensen Fund $5,000 Grant, 2010; MS180.004.009.00012 (Box 9)
    - Christensen Fund Grant, 2004 -- 2006; MS180.004.009.00013 (Box 9)
    - Clark, C.S.: "Africa Trip Report: Ethiopia, Kenya, Sudan", 1986; MS180.004.009.00014 (Box 9)
    - Clark, Lance: RPG: Report on the Ref Influx into NW Somalia, 1986; MS180.004.009.00015 (Box 9)
    - Clay, Jason, 1980 -- 1993; MS180.004.009.00016 (Box 9)
    - Clay, Jason: Articles and Op-Eds, 1989 -- 1990; MS180.004.009.00017 (Box 9)
    - Clay, Jason (Correspondence), 1983 -- 1984; MS180.004.009.00018 (Box 9)
    - Clay, Jason - Feeding the Hand that Bites, 1986 -- 1990; MS180.004.009.00019 (Box 9)
    - Clay, Jason - "Indigenous Models of Tropical Agriculture..", 1985; MS180.004.009.00020 (Box 9)
    - Clay, Jason - Memos/Jason Clay, 1989; MS180.004.009.00021 (Box 9)
    - Clay, Jason - Pichis-Palcazu, 1991; MS180.004.009.00022 (Box 9)
    - Clay, Jason - Power and Famine in Ethiopia, 1985 -- 1986; MS180.004.009.00023 (Box 9)
    - Clay, Jason - Villigization in Ethiopia (rough draft, 1987; MS180.004.009.00024 (Box 9)
    - Clay, J.W. "The West + the Ethiopian Famine: Imps for Humanitarian Asistance", 1987; MS180.004.009.00025 (Box 9)
    - Coalition for Amazonian Peoples and their Environment Annual Meeting Report, 1998; MS180.004.009.00026 (Box 9)
    - Colombia 1 of 2, 1980 -- 2003; MS180.004.009.00027 (Box 9)
    - Colombia 2 of 2, 2005; MS180.004.009.00028 (Box 9)
    - Colombia: Arahuaco -- Yesid Campos, 1980; MS180.004.009.00029 (Box 9)
    - Colombia - CS Contacts in Colombia, 2005; MS180.004.009.00030 (Box 9)
    - Colombia - CS Reports on IPs in Colombia, 2003 -- 2005; MS180.004.009.00031 (Box 9)
    - Colombia - Human Rights in Colombia, Spring, 2005; MS180.004.009.00032 (Box 9)
    - Colombia - IP's in Colombia, 2004 -- 2005; MS180.004.009.00033 (Box 9)
    - Colombia - Kankuamo Case, 2004 -- 2005; MS180.004.009.00034 (Box 9)
    - Colombia: Maps, 2005; MS180.004.009.00035 (Box 9)
    - Colombia: "The Oil Flows, the Forest Bleeds", 2000; MS180.004.009.00036 (Box 9)
    - Colombia - ONIC, 2004 -- 2005; MS180.004.009.00037 (Box 9)
    - Colombia: U'Wa Background Info and Correspondence, 1998; MS180.004.009.00038 (Box 9)
    - Community Products Contract Negotations, 1992; MS180.004.009.00039 (Box 9)
    - Community Products - Contracts and Agreements, 1991 -- 1993; MS180.004.009.00040 (Box 9)
    - Community Products - Correspondence, 1989 -- 1990; MS180.004.009.00041 (Box 9)
    - Community Products - Correspondence, 1991 -- 1992; MS180.004.009.00042 (Box 9)
    - Community Products - Orders, 1989 -- 1990; MS180.004.010.00001 (Box 10)
    - Community Products - Packaging Copy, 1989 -- 1991; MS180.004.010.00002 (Box 10)
    - Community Products - Profile, 1989 -- 1992; MS180.004.010.00003 (Box 10)
    - Community Products - Technical Info, 1991; MS180.004.010.00004 (Box 10)
    - Conferences + International Concerns, MS180.004.010.00005 (Box 10)
    - Constituent Giving History, 2003; MS180.004.010.00006 (Box 10)
      20 years from date of creation.
    - Construction, MS180.004.010.00007 (Box 10)
    - Consultants, 1991; MS180.004.010.00008 (Box 10)
    - Consultants: Development Freelancers, 1991; MS180.004.010.00009 (Box 10)
    - Consultants: Legal Counsel and Management Consulting, 1992; MS180.004.010.00010 (Box 10)
    - Contact Information - Staff, Board, Partners, and Activists, 1998 -- 2009; MS180.004.010.00011 (Box 10)
    - Contacts - Advocacy Contact List - Innu, 2000; MS180.004.010.00012 (Box 10)
    - Copenhagen Women's Conference, 1980; MS180.004.010.00013 (Box 10)
    - Cornell University American Indian Program, 1996; MS180.004.010.00014 (Box 10)
    - Corporate Notes, 2003; MS180.004.010.00015 (Box 10)
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1972 -- 1980; MS180.004.010.00016 (Box 10)
    - Correspondence and Staff Notes, 1998 -- 2007; MS180.004.010.00017 (Box 10)
    - COSTEC, 1993; MS180.004.010.00018 (Box 10)
    - Crafts Center Event Correspondence, 2000; MS180.004.010.00019 (Box 10)
    - Crisp, Jeff F.: "Vol Repatriation Programs for African Refugees", 1984 -- 1986; MS180.004.010.00020 (Box 10)
    - CRS (Catholic Relief Services), 1984 -- 1987; MS180.004.010.00021 (Box 10)
    - CS Descriptions, 2000; MS180.004.010.00022 (Box 10)
    - CSE Dev. Projects Indonesia, 1992; MS180.004.010.00023 (Box 10)
    - CSE Dev. Projects PNG/Solomon Islands, 1992; MS180.004.010.00024 (Box 10)
    - CSE Leaf and Seed Ornaments, 1993; MS180.004.010.00025 (Box 10)
    - CSE Loan Summary, 1991 -- 1993; MS180.004.010.00026 (Box 10)
    - CSE Plans, Reports, and Updates, 1989 -- 1996; MS180.004.010.00027 (Box 10)
    - CSE Projects Brazil, 1992 -- 1993; MS180.004.010.00028 (Box 10)
    - CTTC Center for Traditional Textiles of Cusco (Chinchero) - Chinchero inventory Crafts, 1998; MS180.004.010.00029 (Box 10)
    - CTTC - CTC Correspondence, 1996 -- 1999; MS180.004.010.00030 (Box 10)
    - CTTC - CTC Press/Pamphlets, 1997 -- 1998; MS180.004.010.00031 (Box 10)
    - CTTP Donation Records (El Norte info also), 1996 -- 1999; MS180.004.010.00032 (Box 10)
    - CTTP - Updates/Photos/Info, 1993 -- 2004; MS180.004.010.00033 (Box 10)
    - Cultural Survival Enterprises: Steven Corry/Survival International Accusations, 1992; MS180.004.010.00034 (Box 10)
    - Cultural Survival Fact Sheet, 1991; MS180.004.010.00035 (Box 10)
    - Cultural Survival Info for Ford Foundation - Budget, Staff, Funders, 1989 -- 1992; MS180.004.010.00036 (Box 10)
    - Conger, Lucy Book EL Revised Version 1 of 2, 1994; MS180.004.010.00037 (Box 10)
    - Conger, Lucy Book EL Revised Version 2 of 2, 1994; MS180.004.010.00038 (Box 10)
    - Crahan, Margaret E.: "Catholicism and Human Rights in Latin America", 1989; MS180.004.010.00039 (Box 10)
    - Dams - Background Information, MS180.004.010.00040 (Box 10)
    - Dams - Bonneville Dam of the Columbia River Basin, 1999; MS180.004.010.00041 (Box 10)
    - Dams - China - 3 Gorges Dam, 1996; MS180.004.010.00042 (Box 10)
    - Dams - Edwards Dam, Maine - Kennebec River, 1999; MS180.004.010.00043 (Box 10)
    - Dare Foods - Correspondence, 1990 -- 1993; MS180.004.010.00044 (Box 10)
    - Dare Foods - Harvest from the Rainforest Cookies Copy, 1992; MS180.004.010.00045 (Box 10)
    - Dare Foods Orders, 1990 -- 1992; MS180.004.010.00046 (Box 10)
    - Dare Foods Packaging Copy, 1990 -- 1991; MS180.004.010.00047 (Box 10)
    - Darien Gap, 1996; MS180.004.010.00048 (Box 10)
    - Dean, Bartholomew and Peter H. Herlihy: Best of CSQ Book, 2003; MS180.004.010.00049 (Box 10)
    - Deforestation + Uncontacted Peoples, 2002 -- 2006; MS180.004.010.00050 (Box 10)
    - Defunct Projects - L'Association Tassaght, 1992 -- 1994; MS180.004.010.00051 (Box 10)
    - Deja, 1992 -- 1994; MS180.004.010.00052 (Box 10)
    - Democratic Republic of the Congo (DRC), 2003 -- 2006; MS180.004.011.00001 (Box 11)
    - Development: Dams, 1980 -- 1988; MS180.004.011.00002 (Box 11)
    - Diagnostico Socio-Economico de la Etnia Awa-Kuaiker, 1984; MS180.004.011.00003 (Box 11)
    - DML Send - David Maybury-Lewis Program Fund, 2004; MS180.004.011.00004 (Box 11)
    - Donations, 2005; MS180.004.011.00005 (Box 11)
    - Dossier for Pew Charitable Trust, 1996; MS180.004.011.00006 (Box 11)
    - DPI-NGO, 2005 -- 2007; MS180.004.011.00007 (Box 11)
    - Draft Papers - North America, Africa, and Arctic Overviews, 2002 -- 2004; MS180.004.011.00008 (Box 11)
    - Dream Catchers, 2000; MS180.004.011.00009 (Box 11)
    - Drugs L, 1984 -- 1986; MS180.004.011.00010 (Box 11)
    - Earth Ade, 1991 -- 1992; MS180.004.011.00011 (Box 11)
    - Earth Watch, 2001; MS180.004.011.00012 (Box 11)
    - East Timor, 2002 -- 2004; MS180.004.011.00013 (Box 11)
    - EBazaar Accounting, 1999 -- 2000; MS180.004.011.00014 (Box 11)
    - EBazaar Fair Trade, 1999; MS180.004.011.00015 (Box 11)
    - EBazaar Marketing, 1999; MS180.004.011.00016 (Box 11)
    - EBazaar Orders - Monthly, 1999 -- 2000; MS180.004.011.00017 (Box 11)
    - EBazaar Products, 1999; MS180.004.011.00018 (Box 11)
    - EBazaar Technical, 1999; MS180.004.011.00019 (Box 11)
    - EBazaar Vendors, 1999; MS180.004.011.00020 (Box 11)
    - Ecco Bella Botanicals - Contract, 1993 -- 1994; MS180.004.011.00021 (Box 11)
    - Ecologic, 2007; MS180.004.011.00022 (Box 11)
    - Eco-OK Coffee, 1995; MS180.004.011.00023 (Box 11)
    - ECOSOC Status, 2010; MS180.004.011.00024 (Box 11)
    - Ecuador: Cofan, 2008; MS180.004.011.00025 (Box 11)
    - Ecuador: General, 1978 -- 1998; MS180.004.011.00026 (Box 11)
    - Ecuador: Religion (Missionarie & Indigenous Peoples), 1982; MS180.004.011.00027 (Box 11)
    - Eddy, G. Norman: "Twelve Years at AIC (Some Reminiscences)", 1992; MS180.004.011.00028 (Box 11)
  - Education (Curriculum Resource Program and student conferences), 1975 -- 2006; MS180.004.002
    - Aboriginal Australia - A Cultural Survival Curriculum, 1997; MS180.004.011.00029 (Box 11)
    - Africa Ed Materials, 1994 -- 1999; MS180.004.011.00030 (Box 11)
    - African Case Studies, 1998; MS180.004.011.00031 (Box 11)
    - Australia, 1997; MS180.004.011.00032 (Box 11)
    - Australia Curriculum - 10pt Plan, Mabo, Wik, NTA, 1997; MS180.004.011.00033 (Box 11)
    - Australia Curriculum Research 1 of 3, 1997; MS180.004.011.00034 (Box 11)
    - Australia Curriculum Research 2 of 3, 1997; MS180.004.011.00035 (Box 11)
    - Australia Curriculum Research 3 of 3, 1997; MS180.004.011.00036 (Box 11)
    - Bibliographies, 1996; MS180.004.011.00037 (Box 11)
    - Bibliographies - Resources, 1994; MS180.004.011.00038 (Box 11)
    - Black Mesa Relocation, 1999; MS180.004.011.00039 (Box 11)
    - Blood of our mother: The U'Wa People, Occidental Petroleum, and the Colombian Oil Industry, 1998; MS180.004.011.00040 (Box 11)
    - Chapters: Dineh/Black Mesa, 1999 -- 2001; MS180.004.011.00041 (Box 11)
    - Chiapas 1 of 2, 1992 -- 1996; MS180.004.011.00042 (Box 11)
    - Chiapas 2 of 2, 1998; MS180.004.011.00043 (Box 11)
    - Chiapas Conference Speakers, 1997 -- 2000; MS180.004.011.00044 (Box 11)
    - Chiapas Events 1 of 2, 1998 -- 1999; MS180.004.011.00045 (Box 11)
    - Chiapas Events 2 of 2, 1999; MS180.004.011.00046 (Box 11)
    - The Chiapas Maya (Grades 6-12) Curriculum Guide, 1999; MS180.004.011.00047 (Box 11)
    - Chiapas Nicole's Project, 1999; MS180.004.011.00048 (Box 11)
    - Chiapas Orgs, 1999; MS180.004.011.00049 (Box 11)
    - Chiapas Originals, 1996; MS180.004.011.00050 (Box 11)
    - Chiapas student curr. grades 9-12, 1999; MS180.004.011.00051 (Box 11)
    - Choices for the 21st Century, 2000; MS180.004.011.00052 (Box 11)
    - Choosing our Heroes: Alternatives to Christopher Columbus Course Book, 1998; MS180.004.012.00001 (Box 12)
    - Conference Details, 1998 -- 1999; MS180.004.012.00002 (Box 12)
    - Connections, 2000; MS180.004.012.00003 (Box 12)
    - Conservation and Development in Kenya Student Conference, 1998; MS180.004.012.00004 (Box 12)
    - CRL Student Work + Responses, 1996; MS180.004.012.00005 (Box 12)
    - Cross-Cultural Education, 1982 -- 1996; MS180.004.012.00006 (Box 12)
    - Cultural Survival in the Americas Student Conference, 1996; MS180.004.012.00007 (Box 12)
    - Cultural Survival in the Classroom by Nicole, 1995 -- 1999; MS180.004.012.00008 (Box 12)
    - Current Education Projects, 2000; MS180.004.012.00009 (Box 12)
    - Current Educational Outreach, 1992; MS180.004.012.00010 (Box 12)
    - Curriculum Contacts, 1996 -- 1998; MS180.004.012.00011 (Box 12)
    - Curriculum Development, 1992 -- 1996; MS180.004.012.00012 (Box 12)
    - Curriculum Development - Maintain Curriculum Resources, 1997 -- 1999; MS180.004.012.00013 (Box 12)
    - Curriculum Development - Multi-Cultural Ed., 1994 -- 2001; MS180.004.012.00014 (Box 12)
    - Curriculum Develop't - Curriculum Writing Guidelines, 1999; MS180.004.012.00015 (Box 12)
    - Curriculum Guide Master Copies, 1998 -- 2001; MS180.004.012.00016 (Box 12)
    - Curriculum Program Arts + Culture Module, 1992 -- 1997; MS180.004.012.00017 (Box 12)
    - Curriculum Program Info and Handouts, 1992 -- 1999; MS180.004.012.00018 (Box 12)
    - Curriculum Resource Program Activities Materials, 1998; MS180.004.012.00019 (Box 12)
    - Curriculum Resources - Other Orgs., 1992 -- 1996; MS180.004.012.00020 (Box 12)
    - Curriculum Samples/Models, 2000 -- 2001; MS180.004.012.00021 (Box 12)
    - Defining Indigenous, 2004; MS180.004.012.00022 (Box 12)
    - Development: Development + Education: Africa, 1997; MS180.004.012.00023 (Box 12)
    - Development: Development + Education: Asia, 1997; MS180.004.012.00024 (Box 12)
    - Development: Development + Education: Belize, 1997; MS180.004.012.00025 (Box 12)
    - Development: Developmnet + Education: Brazil - CIMI, 1997; MS180.004.012.00026 (Box 12)
    - Development: Development + Education: Brazil - Guarani, 1994 -- 1997; MS180.004.012.00027 (Box 12)
    - Development: Development + Education: Brazil - Pataxó, 1997; MS180.004.012.00028 (Box 12)
    - Development: Development + Education: Central America, 1997; MS180.004.012.00029 (Box 12)
    - Development: Development + Education: USA - Navajo, 1997; MS180.004.012.00030 (Box 12)
    - Dineh, 1998 -- 1999; MS180.004.012.00031 (Box 12)
    - Ed Curriculum Program, 1995 -- 1996; MS180.004.012.00032 (Box 12)
    - Educat Program - Curriculum Resource Program Manual & Info, 1999; MS180.004.012.00033 (Box 12)
    - Educat Program - Working Model Proposal for CS Education Program, 2000; MS180.004.012.00034 (Box 12)
    - Education 1 of 3, 1998; MS180.004.012.00035 (Box 12)
    - Education 2 of 3, 1999 -- 2001; MS180.004.012.00036 (Box 12)
    - Education 3 of 3, 1975 -- 2003; MS180.004.012.00037 (Box 12)
    - Education & Advocacy Program Guidelines, 2001; MS180.004.012.00038 (Box 12)
    - Education & Advocacy Program Guidelines, 2002; MS180.004.012.00039 (Box 12)
    - Education Budget, 1999 -- 2000; MS180.004.012.00040 (Box 12)
    - Education Catalogues, 1995 -- 1997; MS180.004.012.00041 (Box 12)
    - Education Contacts List, 2000; MS180.004.012.00042 (Box 12)
    - Education Curriculum and Programming Focus Group Report, 2004; MS180.004.012.00043 (Box 12)
    - Education Department, 1996 -- 1997; MS180.004.012.00044 (Box 12)
    - Education Grant Book, 1997; MS180.004.012.00045 (Box 12)
    - Education Materials, 1997 -- 2001; MS180.004.012.00046 (Box 12)
    - Education - Nicole Thornton, 1998; MS180.004.012.00047 (Box 12)
    - Education Outreach Workshops, 1992; MS180.004.012.00048 (Box 12)
    - Education Program, 2002 -- 2004; MS180.004.012.00049 (Box 12)
    - Education - Teacher Evaluations, 1996; MS180.004.012.00050 (Box 12)
    - Educational Curriculum Membership Forms and Correspondence, 1997 -- 1999; MS180.004.013.00001 (Box 13)
    - Educational Curriculum - Mining, 2001; MS180.004.013.00002 (Box 13)
    - Educational Outreach, 1990 -- 1992; MS180.004.013.00003 (Box 13)
    - Environmental Education Curriculum, 2000; MS180.004.013.00004 (Box 13)
    - Fall 2000 Conference - Connections: Working Toward Partnership Building with I.P. 1 of 2, MS180.004.013.00005 (Box 13)
    - Fall 2000 Conference - Connections: Working Toward Partnership Building with I.P. 2 of 2, MS180.004.013.00006 (Box 13)
    - Fall 2001 Student Conference 1 of 2, MS180.004.013.00007 (Box 13)
    - Fall 2001 Student Conference 2 of 2, MS180.004.013.00008 (Box 13)
    - Fall 2002 Student Conf. Yanomami, MS180.004.013.00009 (Box 13)
    - Global Ed/World Affairs Council, 2000; MS180.004.013.00010 (Box 13)
    - Goal 3 Geography, 1999; MS180.004.013.00011 (Box 13)
    - Good Things Happen..., 1997; MS180.004.013.00012 (Box 13)
    - Guide for Teaching Ancient China for Teachers of Grades 3-8, 2002; MS180.004.013.00013 (Box 13)
    - High School Misc. Curriculum, 1999; MS180.004.013.00014 (Box 13)
    - History of ed. dept. letters/exit memos - Education Coordinator Lena Mortensen's Exit memo, 1996; MS180.004.013.00015 (Box 13)
    - History of ed. dept. letters/exit memos - Education Department Objectives by Nicole, 1997 -- 1999; MS180.004.013.00016 (Box 13)
    - History of ed. dept. letters/exit memos - Eliza Hoyt's Exit Memo, 1999 -- 2000; MS180.004.013.00017 (Box 13)
    - History of ed. dept. letters/exit memos - Erica's Projects, 2000 -- 2001; MS180.004.013.00018 (Box 13)
    - History of ed. dept. letters/exit memos - K. Stern's Educ & Advocacy Exit Memo, 2000; MS180.004.013.00019 (Box 13)
    - History of ed. dept. letters/exit memos - K. Stern's exit memo on ImagiNation, 2000; MS180.004.013.00020 (Box 13)
    - History of ed. dept. letters/exit memos - Letter of Inquiry for funding, 1997; MS180.004.013.00021 (Box 13)
    - History of ed. dept. letters/exit memos - Projects CS Educ Interns Office Protocols + Assignments, 2000; MS180.004.013.00022 (Box 13)
    - Human Rights Educators - Sovereignty Curriculum, 2000; MS180.004.013.00023 (Box 13)
    - Hydroelectric Dams and Indigenous Protest, 1999; MS180.004.013.00024 (Box 13)